(ay, ay, ay)
♪ I'm holding on your rope
♪ Got me ten feet off the ground
♪ And I'm hearing what you say
♪ But I can't just make a sound
(ay, ay, ay)
♪ You tell me that you need me
♪ Then you go and cut me down
♪ But wait
♪ You tell me that you're sorry
♪ Didn't think I'd turn around
♪ And say
♪ That it's too late
to apologize
♪ It's too late
(ay, ay, ay)
♪ I said it's too late
to apologize
♪ It's too late
(ay, ay, ay)
♪ Oh
♪ Oh, oh
(ay, ay, ay)
♪ Take another chance
♪ Take a fall,
take a shot for you
♪ Oh, I need you
like a heart needs a beat
♪ But it's nothing new
♪ Yeah, yeah
♪ I loved you with a fire
♪ And now it's turning blue
♪ And you say
♪ Sorry like the angel
♪ Heaven let me think was you
♪ But I'm afraid
♪ It's too late to apologize
♪ It's too late
(ay, ay, ay)
♪ I said, it's too late
to apologize
♪ It's too late
(ay, ay, ay)
♪ Whoa, oh
♪ It's too late to apologize
♪ It's too late
(ay, ay, ay)
♪ I said, it's too late
to apologize
♪ It's too late
(ay, ay, ay)
♪ I said, it's too late
to apologize
♪ Yeah
(ay, ay, ay)
♪ I said, it's too late
to apologize
♪ Yeah
♪ I'm holding on your rope
♪ Got me ten feet
♪ Off
♪ The ground